biggerbras.com 2019-12-10

# Big Girls Bras Privacy Policy and Security Information

General Information  
BGB strives to provide a quality shopping experience for all of our visitors. We regard our customers' privacy with respect and in accordance with acceptable internet practice we have a published privacy policy, which is outlined below.

Customer Information  
BGB does not release or sell email addresses obtained through our website or other activities. All personal information is held as "strictly confidential" by BGB.

BGB does not release or sell the names and addresses of its customers obtained through its website or other activities. All personal information is held as "strictly confidential" by BGB.

Packaging  
BGB mails your package in a plain white poly-vinyl envelope, a standard Post Office priority box, or a plain brown box. The return label reads: BGB - PO Box 590250 - Ft. Lauderdale, FL 33359. No indication of the contents of the package is visible on the package except for the word "clothing" and the value of the contents when needed for Canadian, European or other international customs stickers.

Cookies

Our web site uses cookie technology to place items in your shopping cart and provide an enhanced shopping experience. If you disabled cookies in the past, please make sure that you have cookies enabled (the default setting when you installed your browser software) on your browser in order to place your order online. If you do not wish to enable cookies, please phone in your order.

Cookies are also used by some of the search engines such as Overture to help us determine which "keywords" are searched most frequently by our customers making purchases. This information remains anonymous and is a tally only of specific keywords.

Big Girls' Bras uses pixels, or transparent GIF files, to help manage online advertising. These GIF files are provided by our ad management partners. These files enable our ad management partners to recognize a unique cookie on your Web browser, which in turn enables us to learn which advertisements bring users to our website. The cookie was placed by us or by another advertiser, or advertising partner. With both cookies and Spotlight technology, the information that we collect and analyze is anonymous and not personally identifiable. It does not contain your name, address, telephone number, credit card information, or email address.

Additionally, a cookie may be used so that our web site "remembers" who you are when you use one of our premium services so that only information that is important to you is displayed. No personally identifying information is ever collected using cookies.

Our website uses list technology to remarket our services to visitors and shoppers to our site. This technology is similar to cookie technology. No personal identifying information is stored on our site or used by our company in our remarketing campaigns. This technology allows us to present ads on other websites across the internet to users after they have visited or purchased from our site.

Third Party Cookies for Advertising Purposes  
Our website uses the remarketing features of Google adwords. Third party vendors, including Google, use cookies to serve ads based on a user's prior visits to our website. You may opt out of Google's use of cookies by visiting [the Google advertising opt-out page](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html). You may opt-out of third party vendor's use of cookies by visiting [the Network Advertising Initiative opt out page](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp).

BGB receives thousands of visitors each day to our website and we reserve the right to modify or adapt this policy to further protect the privacy of our visitors, the security, aesthetics and functionality of our site, and to provide a quality shopping experience for our customers.

Credit Cards and Security  
BGB uses the secure server software (SSL) encryption to protect your personal data so that the personal information you provide to complete your purchase remains confidential and secure. BGB uses [Plug 'n Pay Technologies, Inc.](http://www.plugnpay.com/) as our gateway for secure commerce transactions. Your personal and credit card information is used only to process your order, is protected under our agreement with Plug-n-Pay, and is not shared with any other person(s) or entity, including employees of Big Girls Bras.

SSL technology encrypts all of your personal information including credit card number, name, and address, so that it cannot be read as the information travels over the Internet.

If you are using Internet Explorer as your browser, you can verify that you are on a secure page when you see the closed-lock icon. Other browsers should also display some sort of icon to you indicating that the page is secure. You can also click on this icon to see the issuing authority for the secure certificate that makes the SSL possible.

Validation of Digital Certificate  
Our secure checkout uses [Trustwave's digital certificate](https://www.trustwave.com/) so that you know that you are on the BiggerBras.com official website. On Internet Exporer, this technology turns the address bar green and shows you that the site is identified by Trustwave, you can click the lock icon next to the address bar for certificate details.

When You Click the Checkout Button  
You are directed to the secure checkout pages of our website. All secure transactions and informtion from our checikout is encrypted before handled on the Plug-n-Pay gateway. Your credit card information is protected on the Plug-n-Pay secured server and is used only for processing your order. BGB does not save or store your credit card data.

Note: Only the checkout page (which collects and transmits your personal information to the credit card payment center) requires the use of SSL technology. The cart page does not collect or transmit personal data (name, address, and credit card) and therefore does not require SSL.

In accordance to Visa, Mastercard and American Express rules, our site is scanned by a third party (TrustKeeper) to ensure PCI security standards compliance that is required by the credit card companies.

Order Related Emails and Commercial Email That We Send

Customer Followup Emails  
The most common email that we send are customer followup emails after you place an order with us. We typically send an acknowledgement of the order, a thank you, shipping notification(s) and a review request. Since these emails contain vital information about your order and are not of a marketing nature, you do not need to opt-in to our mailing list to receive them.

Commercial Email (marketing)  
These emails are sent periodically a couple times a month and contain special discount codes, an occasional gift card, new or sale items and other promotional materials. If you wish to receive these types of emails, you'll need to opt-in (subscribe) to our email list.

Special Interest Emails (guides, articles and tips)  
We have a lot of information to share - on fitting, on style, on common faux pas, etc. Sometimes it's just easier to put these tidbits into an email than to hope you'll be able to find it on our website when you need it. We try to keep these emails simple and to the point. If you wish to receive these types of emails, you'll need to opt-in (subscribe) to our email list.

Our Thoughts on SPAM Mail  
We've never met a single person that likes getting tons and tons of email - no matter how good the deal is. So with that in mind, we really strive to keep our emails to a minimum and only send the types of emails that you've expressed an interest.

You're in Control, Opt-Out at Any Time  
To make it as easy as possible for you to opt-out and stop receiving our emails, all of our commercial emails have an unsubscribe link in the footer.

In an effort to reduce the thousands of inappropriate email (i.e. SPAM lists) sent to our customer service address: Effective January, 2004 we no longer send an auto-reply to incoming emails. We also use our own spam-blocking software, so please reference your name or order id in the subject line of your email along with your questions or comments inside the email. Do not send attachments, they will be deleted.

In order to better assist our existing customers, BGB attempts to personally answer all customer inquiries within 24 to 72 hours. Occasionally, responses may take an additional day. If you do not receive a response in this time-frame and your question is not answered in our help section, call us. Our toll free number is 1-866-352-4494.

If you are an existing customer, please include your full name, email address, order date and order-id number in your email, AND complete questions or instructions. One word instructions such as "Cancel" or "Change" can not be processed.
